const flagsEurope = [
  { answers: ['albania', 'republic of albania'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/36/Flag_of_Albania.svg" },
  { answers: ['andorra', 'principality of andorra'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/19/Flag_of_Andorra.svg" },
  { answers: ['armenia', 'republic of armenia'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/2f/Flag_of_Armenia.svg" },
  { answers: ['austria', 'republic of austria'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/41/Flag_of_Austria.svg" },
  { answers: ['azerbaijan', 'republic of azerbaijan'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/dd/Flag_of_Azerbaijan.svg" },
  { answers: ['belarus', 'republic of belarus'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/85/Flag_of_Belarus.svg" },
  { answers: ['belgium', 'kingdom of belgium'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/65/Flag_of_Belgium.svg" },
  { answers: ['bosnia and herzegovina', 'bih', 'b&h', 'bosnia-herzegovina'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/bf/Flag_of_Bosnia_and_Herzegovina.svg" },
  { answers: ['bulgaria', 'republic of bulgaria'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/9a/Flag_of_Bulgaria.svg" },
  { answers: ['croatia', 'republic of croatia'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/1b/Flag_of_Croatia.svg" },
  { answers: ['cyprus', 'republic of cyprus'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d4/Flag_of_Cyprus.svg" },
  { answers: ['czechia', 'czech republic'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/cb/Flag_of_the_Czech_Republic.svg" },
  { answers: ['denmark', 'kingdom of denmark'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/9c/Flag_of_Denmark.svg" },
  { answers: ['estonia', 'republic of estonia'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8f/Flag_of_Estonia.svg" },
  { answers: ['finland', 'republic of finland'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/bc/Flag_of_Finland.svg" },
  { answers: ['france', 'french republic'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/c/c3/Flag_of_France.svg" },
  { answers: ['georgia'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/0f/Flag_of_Georgia.svg" },
  { answers: ['germany', 'federal republic of germany'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/b/ba/Flag_of_Germany.svg" },
  { answers: ['greece', 'hellenic republic', 'hellas'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5c/Flag_of_Greece.svg" },
  { answers: ['hungary'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c1/Flag_of_Hungary.svg" },
  { answers: ['iceland'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/ce/Flag_of_Iceland.svg" },
  { answers: ['ireland', 'republic of ireland'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/45/Flag_of_Ireland.svg" },
  { answers: ['italy', 'italian republic'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/0/03/Flag_of_Italy.svg" },
  { answers: ['kazakhstan', 'republic of kazakhstan'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d3/Flag_of_Kazakhstan.svg" },
  { answers: ['kosovo', 'republic of kosovo'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/1f/Flag_of_Kosovo.svg" },
  { answers: ['latvia', 'republic of latvia'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/84/Flag_of_Latvia.svg" },
  { answers: ['liechtenstein', 'principality of liechtenstein'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/47/Flag_of_Liechtenstein.svg" },
  { answers: ['lithuania', 'republic of lithuania'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/11/Flag_of_Lithuania.svg" },
  { answers: ['luxembourg', 'grand duchy of luxembourg'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/da/Flag_of_Luxembourg.svg" },
  { answers: ['malta', 'republic of malta'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/73/Flag_of_Malta.svg" },
  { answers: ['moldova', 'republic of moldova'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/27/Flag_of_Moldova.svg" },
  { answers: ['monaco', 'principality of monaco'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/ea/Flag_of_Monaco.svg" },
  { answers: ['montenegro'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/64/Flag_of_Montenegro.svg" },
  { answers: ['netherlands', 'the netherlands'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/20/Flag_of_the_Netherlands.svg" },
  { answers: ['north macedonia', 'republic of north macedonia'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/79/Flag_of_North_Macedonia.svg" },
  { answers: ['norway', 'kingdom of norway'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d9/Flag_of_Norway.svg" },
  { answers: ['poland', 'republic of poland'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/1/12/Flag_of_Poland.svg" },
  { answers: ['portugal', 'portuguese republic'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5c/Flag_of_Portugal.svg" },
  { answers: ['romania'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/73/Flag_of_Romania.svg" },
  { answers: ['russia', 'russian federation'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/f/f3/Flag_of_Russia.svg" },
  { answers: ['san marino', 'republic of san marino', 'most serene republic of san marino'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b1/Flag_of_San_Marino.svg" },
  { answers: ['serbia', 'republic of serbia'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/ff/Flag_of_Serbia.svg" },
  { answers: ['slovakia', 'slovak republic'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e6/Flag_of_Slovakia.svg" },
  { answers: ['slovenia', 'republic of slovenia'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f0/Flag_of_Slovenia.svg" },
  { answers: ['spain', 'kingdom of spain'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/9/9a/Flag_of_Spain.svg" },
  { answers: ['sweden', 'kingdom of sweden'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/4/4c/Flag_of_Sweden.svg" },
  { answers: ['switzerland', 'swiss condeferation'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f3/Flag_of_Switzerland.svg" },
  { answers: ['turkey', 'republic of turkey'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b4/Flag_of_Turkey.svg" },
  { answers: ['ukraine'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/49/Flag_of_Ukraine.svg" },
  { answers: ['united kingdom', 'uk'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/a/ae/Flag_of_the_United_Kingdom.svg" },
  { answers: ['vatican city', 'the vatican'], prompt: "https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/00/Flag_of_the_Vatican_City.svg" }
];

export const categories = [
  {
    name: "Flags of Europe",
    value: "europe",
    questions: flagsEurope
  }
]
